Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
University of Chicago. Office of the Vice-President. Records
1937-1946
29.75 linear feet (59 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
A former advertising executive, William Benton served as a part-time Vice-President from 1937-1945 and was primarily responsible for the university's public affairs and broadcasting activities. This collection contains the records and correspondence of the University of Chicago's Office of the Vice-President, comprising the administration of William Benton. Included are correspondence, reports, publications, and other administrative records related to university events and issues within his mandate; as well as material related to Benton's broadcasting, public relations, and media relations work on behalf of the university. The collection contains a significant number of items related to the production of the University of Chicago's well-known Round Table radio program, broadcast nationwide from 1933-1955.
Information on Use
Access
The collection is open for research.
Historical Note
Originally an advertising executive and broadcasting entrepreneur, William Benton retired from the advertising world in 1935 and accepted an offer from the University of Chicago's president, Robert M. Hutchins, to undertake a short term study of the university's public relations. After completing the study, Benton assumed the post of part-time vice-president in 1937, overseeing the university's public affairs and broadcasting initiatives until 1945.
As part of Benton's plan to improve the University of Chicago's public image in the wake of accusations that it was a haven for left-wing radicalism, as well as to increase its visibility and prestige, both Benton and Hutchins gave a great number of public talks, especially to the business community. Moreover, Benton's office arranged for Hutchins and prominent faculty members to write articles and be interviewed as experts for various media.
One of Benton's most successful projects was the University of Chicago's Round Table radio program, which was launched as a local broadcast in 1931 and was picked up by the National Broadcasting Company (NBC) in 1933. It was thereafter aired as a national broadcast until 1955. The Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, a private trust providing grants for projects related to science, technology, and economic performance, began sponsoring the weekly broadcasts in 1938.
The standard Round Table format involved three speakers, usually two university faculty members and one guest speaker, and dealt with contemporary – often controversial – social, political and economic issues. Though it quickly emerged as one of the most popular radio programs of the time, it was also criticized for having a leftist bias, especially by NBC. The latter pushed for more network control over its content and sought to impose commercial standards on its scholarly approach. Alfred P. Sloan, himself, criticized the program after a 1945 broadcast in which the liberal economist and philosopher Friedrich Hayek faced off with two faculty members, Charles E. Merriam and Maynard C. Krueger. Sloan viewed the program as unfairly harsh in its treatment of Hayek, and this temporarily jeopardized the program's relationship with the Foundation. During the Second World War, most of the Round Table's programming was related to developments in the war and the American military effort.
Benton also successfully launched the radio program The Human Adventure, which aired 1939-1945. The program showcased faculty research on a wide range of topics, including scientific, historical and cultural phenomena; however, it was less successful than the Round Table at attracting a broad audience. Aside from radio, Benton was keen to develop the University of Chicago's capacity for producing educational films, but his efforts in this realm were not as fruitful as his radio endeavors.
In early 1942, Benton was appointed by the U.S. War Department as Coordinator of the Orientation Courses of the Bureau of Public Relations for the Sixth Corps Area (comprising Illinois, Wisconsin and Michigan). This position involved organizing lectures on different regions of the world, political developments, and international relations for the officer orientation courses held by the various Midwestern military camps of this area. In 1945, Benton officially left the university, accepting the position of Assistant Secretary of State for Public Affairs, which involved consolidating wartime information agencies and creating new information bodies for the post-war era.
Scope Note
The collection is composed primarily of the correspondence of Benton and his associates involved in public relations and broadcasting at the University of Chicago. As well as incoming and outgoing correspondence of William Benton, there is also correspondence of Benton's assistant John P. Howe, and Sherman Dryer, Radio Director for the university. It also contains correspondence with university administrators and faculty, university donors, trustees, and alumni, the commercial publishing and broadcasting community, and a broad array of well-known figures in politics, film, athletics and other fields. A large part of the collection is devoted to the University of Chicago's broadcasting projects, which Benton and his associates believed had great educational significance. In particular, it includes materials related to the production of the famous nation-wide Round Table radio program.
Several items within the collection deal with contemporary issues and events at the University of Chicago, including the ongoing debate over President Hutchins' abolition of varsity football in 1939; preparations for celebrations for the fiftieth anniversary of the university in 1942; logistics for bringing in special guest speakers and researchers, and the university's public relations in the wake of accusations in the mid-1930s that it was a haven for left-wing radicalism. The collection also deals with Benton's and the University of Chicago's activities during the Second World War.
The collection is organized alphabetically, with individual files for each academic year (not calendar year) from 1937-1946. The bulk of this collection spans the years 1937-1946 and the tenure of William Benton as Vice-President. A few letters from 1936 are filed with reference to events that occurred in academic year 1937-1938.
Related Resources
The following related resources are located in the Department of Special Collections:
http://www.lib.uchicago.edu/e/spcl/select.html
Benton, William. Papers
University of Chicago. Office of the President. Hutchins Administration. Records
Subject Headings
Benton, William, 1900-1973; Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899-; University of Chicago -- Administration; University of Chicago. Office of the Vice President; University of Chicago -- Public relations; University of Chicago Round Table (Series)
INVENTORY
- A, general, 1937-1938, Advertising Age Allen, James American Council on Education Anderson, Arthur Anderson, W. France Anthony, Robert O. Atkinson, Carroll Avery, Sewell (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A, general, 1939-1940, Abbott Memorial Fund Adair, Fred L. Adams, James Adler, Mortimer "Adventures in Science" Program Aikman, Duncan Akers, Milburn P. Allen, J. W. Allen, Philip S. Allison, S. K. Alumni Reunion American Alumni Council American Association of Advertising Agencies American Association for Adult Education American Committee for Christian Refugees American Historical Association American Institute of Motion Pictures American Mercury Andersen, Arthur Anderson, Corliss D. Anthropology, Department of Armour Fund Arnett, Trevor Association of School Film Libraries Avery, Sewell Axelrod, Charles (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A, general, 1940-1941, Abbott Laboratories Abbott Memorial Hall Abbott, John Academy of Political Science Action Film Company Adams, Roger Adler, Mortimer Adult Education Council Aikman, Duncan Albertson, M. Aldis, Mrs. Arthur Allen, B. P. Allison, S. K. Alumni Magazine American Council, Institute of Pacific Relations American Council on Education American Council on Public Relations American Institute of Meat Packers American Picture American Institute of Motion Pictures American Poet Andersen, Arthur Anderson, M. D., Trust Indenture Arnett, Trevor Arnspiger, Victor Ashcroft, Sam (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A, general, 1941-1942, Abbott, Edith Abbott Laboratories Abeles, Mrs. Jerome Action Film Company Adams, George H. Adams, James Luther Adler, Max Adler, Mortimer Albertson, M. Aldrich, Malcolm P. Allen, Edward Allen, Floyd A. Allen, Ted Alumni Office American Association of Scientific Workers American Friends of China American Geographical Society American Magazine American Political Science Association American Political Science Association Anderson, Harry Armstrong, O. K. Arnold, Thurman Association of American Universities Association of School Film Libraries Association of Southern Commissioners of Agriculture Athletic Office Avery, Sewell Ayer, N. W. & Son (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A, general, 1942-1943, Adelphi College Adler, Mortimer Advisory Commission on Industrial Research Aitchison, Robert J. Alexander, Will W. Alumni American Security Company of New York American University Asher, Louis E. Axelson, Charles F. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A, general, 1943-1944, Adair, Fred Addis, Nata Albertson, Maurice Ambler, Kirby P. Anderson, Harold Arant, Douglas Associated Press (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A, general, 1944-1945, Adair, Fred L. Ahrens Publishing Company Allee, W.C. America's Town Meeting Anderson, Harold A. Andrews, Lois Armstrong, George S. Arnold, Thurman Ascoli, Mrs. Max Austin, Warren R. Averitt, W. G. Avery, Sewell (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A, general, 1945-1946, Adler, Mortimer American Jewish Conference (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Adler, Mortimer, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Adler, Mortimer, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Adler-Washburne, "Progressive Education Debate," Rotarian, September 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Adult Education, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Adult Education, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Adult Education Board, 1937-1938, Bryson, Lyman Fazerfeltz Research Fisher, Sterling Lewis, William Paley, William Randall, Clarence Rockefeller, Laurance S. Willis, Frederic A. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Adult Education Board, 1939-1940, Bryson, Lyman Fisher, Sterling (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Adult Education Board, 1940-1941, Barr, Stringfellow Bryson, Lyman Coulter, Douglas Fisher, Sterling (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Adult Education Board, 1941-1942, Agenda for meeting, 5 September 1941 Fisher, Sterling Paley, William (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Adult Education Council, Round table announcement, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Advisory Committee on Industrial Research, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ahrens Publishing Company, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Ahrens Publishing Company, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Alumni Authors, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Alumni Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Alumni Foundation, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Alumni Foundation, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Alumni Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Alumni Foundation Honor Roll, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Alumni Council, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- American Association of Scientific Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Army Training Program, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Avery, Sewell, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Avery, Sewell, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aviation, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Aviation, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- B, general, 1937-1938, Bachmeyer, Arthur G. Baldwin, Ganson Baldwin, Major Norman Lee Barclay, Frances Barreau, Leon Bates, Wallace Belser, R. B. Bequest Program for Alumni, Outline of Berkson, Seymour Bernays, Edward L. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- B, general, 1937-1938, Bigelow, Harry Bishop, H. S., Curtis Publishing Company Blagden, F. Merdith, Harvard University Blake, Tiffany Blinder, A. L., Esquire Bliss, G. A. Blodgett, Harvey A. Bodfish, John, First Federal Savings and Loan Booz, Edwin G. Borgese, G. A. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- B, general, 1937-1938, Brandt, Carl Breckinridge, Sophonisba Bricken, Mrs. K. Bristol, Henry Brown, Dan Brownlow, Louis Buford, Cornelius Buildings and Grounds Bunzell, H. H. Burnett, Hal Business Screen Buswell, Guy Butler, Mrs. Nathaniel (Box 2, Folder 14)
- B, general, 1939-1940, Bacher, George Banfe, Charles Barnard, Harrison Bays, Alfred W. Beaven, J. C. Benson, Purnell Berkson, Eleanor Berkson, Seymour Bernstein, Marcus (Box 2, Folder 15)
- B, general, 1939-1940, Blackett, Will Bond, William S. Bloom, William Bone, Avelina Boneer, Robert Jr. Booz, Edwin G. Borgese, G. A. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- B, general, 1939-1940, Bracher, Carl Bradshaw, S. B. Brandenburg, George Brandt, Carl Braymer, Marjorie Breasted, Charles Breckinridge, Sophonisba Browder, Earl Brumbaugh, A. J. Bucy, Paul Buildings and Grounds Bursar Buswell, Guy T. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- B, general, 1940-1941, Bachhofer, Ludwig Bachman, Harold Bailey, David A. Baker, Erle Baker, John C. Barnard, Eunice Barr, Palham Barr, Stringfellow Barton, Bruce Batchelder, W. O. Batten, Barton, Dustine & Osborne Bays, Alfred W. Beacom Beck, Thomas Beem, Mrs. Maurice Bentley, Elizabeth King Benton & Bowles Berrien Springs, Michigan Berwanger, Jay (Box 2, Folder 18)
- B, general, 1940-1941, Blackett, Sample, Hummert Inc. Blaine, Mrs. Emmons Blair, Walter Bloch, Robert Block, Philip Bohan, R. T. Bond, William Scott Borgese, G. A. Bostick, W. F. Boston University Boyer, Allison (Box 2, Folder 19)
- B, general, 1940-1941, Brackney, H. W. Briggs, Thomas Broadcasting Magazine Brown, C. S. Brown, John Crosby Brown, Lewis H. Brown, Mimi Brownlow, Louis Brumbaugh, A. J. Brummerstedt, Marian Burgess, E. W. Buswell, Guy T. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- B, general, 1941-1942, Bachmeyer, A. C. Baker, M. Baldridge, Cyrus Le Roy Baldwin, Hanson Bane, Frank Banfield, Paul Bard, Ralph Barden, John Barker, Granville Barker, Wayne Barnard, Harry Barnum, H. H. Barr, Stringfellow Bartky, Walter Bay, Emmett Beck, Dewey Becker, Dr. Bell, Ray Berle, A. A. Bethke, Robert (Box 2, Folder 21)
- B, general, 1941-1942, Biechler, E. C. Billings, John Shaw Brigham, Alfred Biow Company Black, John Blackett, Hill Blackfriars Bliss, H. H. Block, Hal Boothe, Clare Luce Blum, Mary Borchard, Edwin Borgese, G. A. Boyes, Watson (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Br, general, 1941-1942, Brentano's Bretz, J. Harlan Brewington, Ann Briggs, Lyman J. Bro, Margueritte Bromage, W. H. Brook, Arthur Brown, Arthur Brown, Albert Brown, George R. Brown, Mark Brown, Mimi Brown, Richard Brownlow, Louis Brumbaugh, A. J. Buck, Allen Bucknell University Buell, Raymond Leslie Bullis, Harry A. Burger, Baird Burnett, Hal Burnham, John Burton, Mr. Bush, Vannevar Buswell, Guy Butler, Ralph Starr (Box 2, Folder 23)
- B, general, 1942-1943, Bachmeyer, A. C. Barnett, C. A. Barr, Stringfellow Bartky, Walter Barrows, A. S. Batchelor, Bronson Baumer, Franklin Bean, Donald Beaven, Joe Beck, Thomas Berk, Mr. and Mrs. S. B. Berk, Roger Bernhart, V. Richard (Box 3, Folder 1)
- B, general, 1942-1943, Blair, W. McCormick Boardman, F. W., Jr. Bovee, Arthur G. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- B, general, 1942-1943, Brakeley, George A. Brooks, Walker Brooks, Wallace Brown, James, IV Brumbaugh, Aaron J. Burgess, Ernest Burke, Harry Buswell, Guy Butler, Ralph S. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- B, general, 1943-1944, Bachmeyer, A. C. Bane, Frank Barnard, Harry Bartky, Walter Bartlett, K. G. Bean, Donald Bedford, F. H. Benchley, Robert Bert, Hardy (Box 3, Folder 4)
- B, general, 1943-1944, Binder, Carroll Bishop, Ethel Bloch, Henry Blucher, Walter Boyden, Polly Burt, Hardy (Box 3, Folder 5)
- B, general, 1943-1944, Breasted, Charles Brown, George Brown, John Brumbaugh, Aaron Buchanan, Scott Buchbinder, Hazel Buchman, Sidney Burke, Eugene Burke, Julia Burke, M. L. Burns, Robert Butterly, George (Box 3, Folder 6)
- B, general, 1944-1945, Bachmeyer, A. C. Bailey, Thomas A. Baldwin, Roger N. Ball, Joseph Barclay, John A. Barlow, Arthur Beal Beard, Charles Beck, Charlton Bell, Laird Berge, Wendell (Box 3, Folder 7)
- B, general, 1944-1945, Blair, W. McCormick Boardman, True Bogert, George C. Borgese, G. A. Bovee, Arthur (Box 3, Folder 8)
- B, general, 1944-1945, Brady, Robert A. Brecher, Edward Bretz, J. Harlan Brown, Arthur Brown, George H. Brumbaugh, A. J. Brumbaugh, T. T. Buchanan, Douglas Buildings Named after Chicagoans Burbach, G. M. Bush, P. S. Buswell, Guy T. Butler, Burridge (Box 3, Folder 9)
- B, general, 1945-1946, Bachmeyer, A. C. Beal, John Bissell, Frederick Bostwick, C. A. Braden, Spruelle Brakeley, G. A. Brandt, Joseph Briscoe, Traver Brown, Ruth Buck, Pearl Bull, Helen Burnett, Hugh Butler, Burridge Butler, Paul (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bachmeyer, A. C., 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bachmeyer, A. C., 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Baptist Theological Union, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Baptist Theological Union, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Barden, John, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Barr, Stringfellow, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Barr, Stringfellow, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Beals, Ralph A., 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Beals, Ralph A., 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Beals, Ralph A., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Beals, Ralph A., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Bean, Donald, press matters and fiftieth anniversary matters, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Bean, Donald, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Bean, Donald, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Beck, Charlton, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Beck, Charlton, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Beck, Charlton, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Beck, Charlton, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Beck, Charlton, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Beck, Charlton, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Believe it Or Not, Ripley's, words of American origin, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Bell, Laird, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bell, Laird, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bell, Laird, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bell, Laird, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bell, Laird, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bell, Laird, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Benton, William B., November-March, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Benton, William B., April-June, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Benton, William B., March-June, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Benton, William B., July-October, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Benton, William B., November-February, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Benton, William B., February-April, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Benton, William B., May-June, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Benton, William B., July-October, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Benton, William B., November-January, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Benton, William B., January-March, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Benton, William B., April-June, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Benton, William B., July-October, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Benton, William B., November-December, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Benton, William B., Round Table, "Censorship", 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Benton, William B., Round Table, "Radio in Wartime", 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Benton, William B., April-June, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Benton, William B., July-October, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Benton, William B., November-March, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Benton, William B., July-November, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Benton, William B., December-January, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Benton, William B., February-June, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Benton, William B., July-December, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Benton, William B., January-June, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Benton, William B., biographical, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Benton, William B., biographical, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bernays, Edward L, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Bernays, Edward L., 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bernays, Edward L., 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bethke, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Biechler, E. G., 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Blackett, Hill, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Blair, William McCormick, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees, docket materials with special interest stories, 1937-1938 about certain gifts (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees, May presentation, students at the University of, Chicago, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees, December presentation, Committee on Development, public relations history and activities, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Board of Trustees, January presentation, Hospital-Medical, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees, November presentation, financial position of the University (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees, including "From Harper to Hutchins," Christian Century, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Board of Trustees, November presentation, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Board of Trustees, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Board of Trustees, minutes of meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees, minutes of Committee meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Bowker, Marjorie, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Brady, Robert A., 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Brandt, Carl, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Brandt, Joseph A., 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Brandt, Joseph A., 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Brakeley, George, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Brakeley, George, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Brashears, J. Arthur, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Brashears, J. Arthur, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Brashears, J. Arthur, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Bricken, Carl, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Bright, Ruth, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Bright, Ruth, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, general, 1939-1940, Radio Committee meeting minutes National Association of Broadcasters Code Harper, C. E. Folde 12: Broadcasting, general, 1940-1941 Schreiber, F. P. Query re: transcript prices (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, general, 1941-1942, Carter, Marian S. Cooperative Analysis of Broadcasting Opinion Parade Release (suggested) re: Howe, Dryer, Shubart, Whitman World-Wide Broadcasting Co. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, general, 1943-1944, Denny, George V. Gershoy, Leo Tyler, I. Keith (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, general, 1945-1946, Kesten, Paul (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, American Broadcasting Company, Hubbell Robinson, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Angell, James R., 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Angell, James R., 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Angell, James R., 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Angell, James R., 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Angell, James R., 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Bacher, William A., 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, Bacher, William A., 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting, Braun, Dorothy, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Broadcasting, Braun, Dorothy, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Broadcasting, British Broadcasting Corporation, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Broadcasting, British Broadcasting Corporation, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Broadcasting, Broadcasting Magazine, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Broadcasting, Brucker, Herbert, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Broadcasting, Budget, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Broadcasting, Budget, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Broadcasting, Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Broadcasting, Campus radio station, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Broadcasting, Chalkey, Lyman, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Broadcasting, Chapel broadcasts, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Broadcasting, Chapel broadcasts, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Broadcasting, Chapel broadcasts, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)